Guide to the Jobs With Justice Audio-Visual Materials 1987-2011
Jobs With Justice Audio-Visual Materials
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Jobs With Justice Audio-Visual Materials, 1987-2011
6369 AV
Jobs With Justice
19.1 linear ft.
Audio cassette tapes, DVDs, VHS video cassette tapes.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Jobs with Justice (JWJ) is a non-profit workers' advocacy organization based in Washington, D.C. Marking its beginning with a convening in Miami in 1987, JWJ started with members pledging to support others' fights for economic justice, as well as their own. Since that time, Jobs with Justice has grown to forty-five local affiliations in twenty-four states across the United States, and members now pledge to "stand up for our rights as working people to a decent standard of living; support the rights of all workers to organize and bargain collectively; fight for secure family-wage jobs in the face of corporate attacks on working people and our communities; organize the unorganized to take aggressive action to secure a better economic future for all of us; and mobilize those already organized to join the fight for jobs with justice" (http://www.jwj.org/about-us/our- history, accessed 2/7/14).
Jobs with Justice organizes across community lines, working with community, student, faith, and organized labor groups. Significant JWJ campaigns include the Justice for Janitors (1985), Justice at Verizon (1989), Justice at Smithfield (2008).
Communications Workers of America (CWA) President Larry Cohen founded Jobs with Justice in 1987. Since 2007, Sarita Gupta has served as Jobs with Justice's Executive Director. In 2012, American Rights at Work and Jobs with Justice merged.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Jobs With Justice (JWJ)
Form and Genre Terms:
Audio cassette tapes; DVDs; VHS video cassette tapes
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
6369: Jobs With Justice Records
6369 MB: Jobs With Justice Memorabilia
6369 P: Jobs With Justice Photographs
CONTAINER LIST
- Layoff -, 1 (Box 1)
- Unlabeled, 2 (Box 1)
- Unlabeled, 3 (Box 1)
- You are history, you are legend -- International Brigade Veteran Reunion - Nov. 1996, 4 (Box 1)
- Workers' Right Board Hearing -- May 13, 1999, 5 (Box 1)
- Rally - Annual Meeting 2000 -- Raw footage, 6 (Box 1)
- Jobs with Justice - 9/24/2005 - Wal-Mart NWRB hearing, St. Louis, MO -- #3, 7 (Box 1)
- 2000 Student Labor Pre-conf., 8 (Box 1)
- Jobs with Justice - 2005 - St. Louis - Banquet & Celebration -- 9/23/2005, 9 (Box 1)
- Belle Fontaine Rally -- 9/23/2005 -- Annual Meeting, 10 (Box 1)
- JwJ Annual 2001 Cleveland -- Raw footage, 11 (Box 1)
- Jobs with Justice annual meeting February 25-28, 1999 in Louisville, KY, 12 (Box 1)
- Jobs with Justice annual meeting February 25-28, 1999 in Louisville, KY, 13 (Box 1)
- JwJ Annual Mtg. Raw -- Pt. 1, 14 (Box 1)
- Local 46 fighting Privatization, 15 (Box 1)
- Jobs with Justice - 2001 Conference video, 16 (Box 1)
- Unlabeled, 17 (Box 1)
- JwJ - Annual meeting 2001 (tapes 4,5,6) -- Raw footage, 18 (Box 1)
- JwJ - (tapes 7 &8) - WRB hearing -- Raw footage, 19 (Box 1)
- Free Speech TV - Special reports - World in Crisis -- 2/1/2002, 20 (Box 1)
- #17 Jobs with Justice (15) - MB Maxwell / Louisville -- 2/28/1999, 21 (Box 1)
- #18 Jobs with Justice (16) - MB Maxwell / Louisville -- 2/28/1999, 22 (Box 1)
- At the River I Stand, 23 (Box 1)
- Copy Rally -- 9/18, 24 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American dream?, 25 (Box 1)
- 9/28/1995, 26 (Box 1)
- Unlabeled, 27 (Box 1)
- Campus Network/Our future at risk, 1 (Box 2)
- Community partners for affordable accessible healthcare - "Don't touch our Medicaid" 3/23/2003, 2 (Box 2)
- JwJ Conference (2001) - original, 3 (Box 2)
- JwJ News -- Philly -- 2003, 4 (Box 2)
- Solidarity Jobs with Justice -- 2001, 5 (Box 2)
- Vermont Workers' Center -- 2002-2003, 6 (Box 2)
- Justice for Janitors - 2002 [unedited], 7 (Box 2)
- Jobs with Justice SeaTac Airport Action! -- Q13 Morning News, 26 July 2002, 8 (Box 2)
- Bus Cut Rally, Friday -- 9/6/2002, 9 (Box 2)
- The 7000 (Chicago's Hotel contract Fight), 10 (Box 2)
- Jobs with Justice annual meeting February 25-28, 1999 in Louisville, KY, 11 (Box 2)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting, Washington, DC Campus Activism Press Briefing, 12 (Box 2)
- Austin, TX -- CUS/TSEU -- JwJ 12/10/1998, 13 (Box 2)
- Where do you stand?, 14 (Box 2)
- Labor beat: two warriors, 15 (Box 2)
- The World is not for sale, 16 (Box 2)
- Janitor's Strike in Boston -- 10/23/2002, 17 (Box 2)
- TV Coverage: Plant closing -- 8/18/2000, 18 (Box 2)
- Bush protest July 1, 2002 - Downtown Cleveland, Ohio -- Wal-Mart, 19 (Box 2)
- Workers rights board hearing announcement about IBT 964, 20 (Box 2)
- Bulk-O-Matic Labor Board hearing tape 2 -- Local 1964, 21 (Box 2)
- KY - JwJ - 4/3/2003 -- Civil rights, 22 (Box 2)
- Massachusetts Confronts the Recession: A Speak Out for Fairness and Justice in the Economy (tape 1), 23 (Box 2)
- Massachusetts Confronts the Recession: A Speak Out for Fairness and Justice in the Economy (tape 2), 24 (Box 2)
- Urbana - Champaign S26 Events - Highlights, 1 (Box 3)
- JWJ Open Mike Night 7/9/2004 @ Staff and Leader Gathering, 2 (Box 3)
- Outriders, 3 (Box 3)
- Justice for Janitors Washington, DC - Newsclip, 4 (Box 3)
- Bulk-O-Matic Labor Board: Hearing Tape 1 taken by Jeff Kirby - Teamsters Local 964, 5 (Box 3)
- Union Summer 1997 - Recruitment Video, 6 (Box 3)
- A Victory for ESP's - The Living Wage Video - May 2004, 7 (Box 3)
- A Third World - Jesse Vander Does, 8 (Box 3)
- GE CEO Jack Welch's Comments to GE management -- January 6-7, 1997 - Baton Raton, FL, 9 (Box 3)
- V & V Supremo Labor Disagreement - Noticias 66, 10 (Box 3)
- Portland - Teachers WRB - 2/20/2003, 11 (Box 3)
- At Your Service "Workers Rights Board" #284 -- 12/06/2001, 12 (Box 3)
- UCSD Students for Economic Justice "Making the Invisible Visible" - the student & janitor movement at UCSD - 2001, 13 (Box 3)
- Workers Rights Board - At Your Service 12/3/2001, 14 (Box 3)
- Wal-MART in Chicago - 5/24/2001, 15 (Box 3)
- JWJ (RI) TV Coverage of Welfare Hearing - 12/11/1997; RI-JWJ Presentation at RIOP on Living Wage, 16 (Box 3)
- Lockout The People vs Peterbilt, 17 (Box 3)
- Women Organize !, 18 (Box 3)
  c.1
- Women Organize !, 19 (Box 3)
  c.2
- Women Organize !, 20 (Box 3)
  c.3
- Jobs with Justice Workers' Rights Board - Hearing on Health Care - 3/31/2004, 21 (Box 3)
- Jobs with Justice Workers' Rights Board - Hearing on Health Care - 3/31/2004, 22 (Box 3)
- Jobs with Justice Workers' Rights Board - Hearing on Health Care - 3/31/2004, 23 (Box 3)
- Cingular and Verizon Wireless: A Tale of Two Companies -- Communications Workers of America, 24 (Box 3)
- Advocate Health Care: Separate and Unequal, 25 (Box 3)
- Occupation - Narrated by Ben Affleck, 26 (Box 3)
- Occupation - Narrated by Ben Affleck, 27 (Box 3)
- Worker's Rights Board -- October 10, 2002, 28 (Box 3)
- News Coverage of JwJ Health Care Action Day - 10/3/1990, 1 (Box 4)
- News Coverage of JwJ Health Care Action Day - 10/3/1990, 2 (Box 4)
- News Coverage of JwJ Health Care Action Day - 10/3/1990, 3 (Box 4)
- JwJ Health Care Action Week: News Highlights, 6/6/1991, 4 (Box 4)
- JwJ Health Care Action Week: News Highlights, 6/6/1991, 5 (Box 4)
- JwJ Health Care Action Week: News Highlights, 6/6/1991, 6 (Box 4)
- Health Care Protestors at Democratic Convention - June 2 1994, 7 (Box 4)
- Jobs with Justice - Massachusetts -- tape 1-3, 5-8, 8 (Box 4)
- Segments on NYC Health Care Rally -- 2/17/1994, 9 (Box 4)
- Emergency Drive for Health Care - 9/28/1991 -- Rally & News Coverage CWA Local 3511 - Jackson, Miss, 10 (Box 4)
- Maine Emergency Drive for Health Care 1991 - Newark, NJ, 11 (Box 4)
- Health Care Workers Rally - August 24-25, 1994, 12 (Box 4)
- Emergency Drive for Health Care - 9/28/1991 -- Rally & News Coverage CWA Local 3511 - Jackson, Miss, 13 (Box 4)
- Jobs with Justice -- March 1990, 14 (Box 4)
- Jobs with Justice -- March 1990, 15 (Box 4)
- Jobs with Justice -- March 1990, 16 (Box 4)
- Chicago NLRB Sit-ins, 17 (Box 4)
- NLRB - Philadelphia, 18 (Box 4)
- Jobs with Justice: 2001 Conference Video, 19 (Box 4)
- Jobs with Justice: 2001 Conference video, 20 (Box 4)
- Jobs with Justice Healthcare Action Day Newsclips, 21 (Box 4)
- NY Jobs with Justice Healthcare Campaign, 22 (Box 4)
- Kentucky - Sonora Worker Exchange -- Southern Arizona Alliance for Economic Justice, 1 (Box 5)
- Jobs with Justice -- Community Action for Workers' Rights, 2 (Box 5)
- Occupation: A film about the Harvard Living, 3 (Box 5)
- Wake up Wal-Mart -- Rochester, NY -- Nov. 2005, 4 (Box 5)
- Labor Institute of Public Affairs -- There's Supposed to be a Law (1994), 5 (Box 5)
- Jobs with Justice -- 9/24/2005, St. Louis, MO -- #1, 6 (Box 5)
- S.F. JwJ WRB Hearing - Oct. 15 (Min. wage.), 7 (Box 5)
- April 20, 2001 -- DC FTAA rally, 8 (Box 5)
- 2000 - Student Labor Pre-Conf. -- Case Studies, 9 (Box 5)
- Building a Poultry Justice Movement Tyson Strike, 10 (Box 5)
- Building a Poultry Justice Movement Tyson Strike, 11 (Box 5)
- Texas Trail: First-hand in Bush Land, 12 (Box 5)
- MO - JwJ (no other info on the tape), 13 (Box 5)
- Breaking the bonds of structural servitude, UCSC 11/13/2003 -- FTAA Protests Miami -- 11/17-11/21/2003, 14 (Box 5)
- Immigrant workers freedom ride - Rev.. James Lawson - 5/17/2003, Houston Kick-Off Event 6/14/2003, 15 (Box 5)
- Sympathy for Justice -- August 25, 2000 -- NPO, AFSCME, Kentucky, 16 (Box 5)
- 2000 Philly AFSCME Hospital Workers Rally, 17 (Box 5)
- Worker Rights Board Hearing, Knoxville, Tennessee -- The Right to Organize, April 2005, 18 (Box 5)
- Worker's Rights Board -- Portland Oregon, 19 (Box 5)
- JwJ - Rough 1 -- 3/5/2003, 20 (Box 5)
- Jobs w/Justice Compilation -- Nov. 23, 1987 -- MASTER, 21 (Box 5)
- Unlabeled, 22 (Box 5)
- UFCW a Voice for working America -- "Walmart's War on Workers", 1 (Box 6)
- Hamlet, NC: Our Jobs, Our Lives?, 2 (Box 6)
- Morristown -- Video Letters, 3 (Box 6)
- Morristown -- Video Letters, 4 (Box 6)
- Longshoreman's Assoc. - K. Riley, Charleston - 10/24/1999, 5 (Box 6)
- How to start a Christian County Chapter with Guy Rodgers for Christian Coalition Leadership School, 6 (Box 6)
- Globalization for beginners workshop, 7 (Box 6)
- JwJ -- 7/21/2000, 8 (Box 6)
- Solidarity Presents National United Students Against Sweatshops@ University of Michigan Rally 1/17/2000, 9 (Box 6)
- JwJ Workers' Rights Board -- 2/26/2002, 10 (Box 6)
- TABD Demo Chicago -- 11/2002, 11 (Box 6)
- Inter Park HQ, Downtown DC -- 9/26/2000, 12 (Box 6)
- Goodyear Leaflet -- 12/16/2006, 13 (Box 6)
- Unlabeled, 14 (Box 6)
- 2000 Student - Labor Pre-Conf., 15 (Box 6)
- Jobs with Justice - Tape #3, 16 (Box 6)
- Steelworkers Contract with America, 17 (Box 6)
- Building a Poultry Justice Movement (UFCW), 18 (Box 6)
- On the Road at Overnite, 19 (Box 6)
- Unlabeled, 20 (Box 6)
- DANGER AHEAD! The FTAA is Coming Our Way A Mass. Jobs with Justice Video, February, 2001, 1 (Box 7)
- Danger Ahead! -- Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 2 (Box 7)
- Danger Ahead! -- Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 3 (Box 7)
- Excerpts from Danger Ahead! -- A Jobs with Justice organizing video -- Feb. 5, 2001, 4 (Box 7)
- AirCheck "Tejano Racism / Sony Discos Visit / Rally", 5 (Box 7)
- Sprint Action -- Washington, DC -- TRT 646, 6 (Box 7)
- Lincoln's Living Legacy -- 9/19/1995, 7 (Box 7)
- Colorado JwJ Footage, 8 (Box 7)
- Jobs with Justice - Meeting Opener - Rough Cut -- 3/11/2003, 9 (Box 7)
- Building a Poultry Justice Movement Tyson Strike, 10 (Box 7)
- I Poland, 11 (Box 7)
- JwJ: Denver, Labor Day, 12 (Box 7)
- Unlabeled, 13 (Box 7)
- Unlabeled, 14 (Box 7)
- Morristown -- Video Cartas -- Spanish, 15 (Box 7)
- Wood - Jobs with Justice -- 2/26/1999 -- Louisville, KY, 16 (Box 7)
- Jobs with Justice -- Wal-Mart NWRB Hearing -- 9/24/2005 - St. Louis, MO -- #2, 17 (Box 7)
- Richmark/Oakwood - Religion Labor Pre. Conf., 18 (Box 7)
- Rhode Island Welfare Rights Hearing -- News Coverage and video, 19 (Box 7)
- Workers' Rights Board Workforce Hearing -- 3/11/1997, 20 (Box 7)
- JwJ Rally - June 20, 1997 -- Pine Bluff, Ark., 21 (Box 7)
- Chicago Jobs with Justice -- A Campaign for Workers Rights, 22 (Box 7)
- Jobs with Justice -- Interview - Duluth, MN, 23 (Box 7)
- Workers Rights Board/Standard Drywall, 24 (Box 7)
- At the River I Stand, 25 (Box 7)
- At the River I Stand, 26 (Box 7)
- Strawberries: The Fruit of Injustice, 1 (Box 8)
- Jobs with Justice - March 1990, 2 (Box 8)
- Jobs with Justice - March 1990, 3 (Box 8)
- Jobs with Justice - March 1990, 4 (Box 8)
- We Stand Together - CWA 50th Anniversary Video - 8/24/1988, 5 (Box 8)
- On the Road at Overnite, 6 (Box 8)
- Disability Nightmare -- Workplace Injury Litigation Group, Inc. (Spanish), 7 (Box 8)
- Disability Nightmare -- Workplace Injury Litigation Group, Inc. (1996), 8 (Box 8)
- At Your Service #273 -- "The WTO & You" -- 8/23/2001, 9 (Box 8)
- Struggle in the Heartland, 10 (Box 8)
- Jobs with Justice, 11 (Box 8)
- Jobs with Justice, 12 (Box 8)
- Jobs with Justice, 13 (Box 8)
- No Time for hate -- Online Revised, 14 (Box 8)
- America's Victory: the 1997 UPS Strike, 15 (Box 8)
- AFUERA de las Sombras: Una Historia del Corazon de America, 16 (Box 8)
- Workers' Rights Board Hearing - March 11, 1997 -- On Workfare - Edited for TV, 17 (Box 8)
- Austin Cablevision Demonstration -- Jobs with Justice Conference -- Feb. 21, 1992, 18 (Box 8)
- Witness: Justice @ Smithfield, 19 (Box 8)
- Texas Trail: First-hand in Bush Land, 20 (Box 8)
- Jobs with Justice - A movement that's working, 21 (Box 8)
- Jobs with Justice - A movement that's working, 22 (Box 8)
- Jobs with Justice - A movement that's working, 1 (Box 9)
- CWA -- Jobs with Justice -- News Clips - June 22, 1987, 2 (Box 9)
- Jobs with Justice: A movement that's working -- 4/1990, 3 (Box 9)
- Economic Justice Slideshow -- Training video, 4 (Box 9)
- Jobs with Justice -- 3/22/1990 MASTER, 5 (Box 9)
- Sweat Shops, 6 (Box 9)
- Bob Muehlenkamp -- JwJ slide show presentation, 7 (Box 9)
- Jobs with Justice -- 1992, 8 (Box 9)
- CWA -- Jobs with Justice -- News Conference -- 6/22/1987, 9 (Box 9)
- December 8, 1998 -- WHAS-TV 6 pm -- Jobs with Justice, 10 (Box 9)
- Media Clips -- May 27, 1993, 11 (Box 9)
- Late 90's, 12 (Box 9)
- JwJ Economics Slide Show - Bob's Presentation in Austin -- 2/22 & 23/1992, 13 (Box 9)
- Jobs with Justice, 14 (Box 9)
- Newsies, 15 (Box 9)
- Labor Law Reform - News Clips MASTER, 16 (Box 9)
- Jobs with Justice TV News Highlights -- June-December 1987, 17 (Box 9)
- NLRB - Sit-ins, 1993; 18 (Box 9)
- Emergency Ambulance Drive News Clips for Citizen Action Coalition - 12/1991, 19 (Box 9)
- Florida Jobs with Justice -- Television News Highlights -- 8/6/1987, 20 (Box 9)
- Cabin Creek Center -- Emergency Drive -- 10/8/1991, 21 (Box 9)
- Another World is Possible: North American Voices at the World Social Forum, 22 (Box 9)
- Kentucky - Sonora Worker Exchange -- Southern Arizona Alliance for Economic Justice, 23 (Box 9)
- Jobs with Justice, 24 (Box 9)
- UFCW: a VOICE for working America -- Holding the Line: The Southern California Supermarket Strike/Lockout - January 2004, 1 (Box 10)
- Jobs with Justice - 2003 Conference Video, 2 (Box 10)
- Jobs with Justice - 2003 Conference Video, 3 (Box 10)
- Jobs with Justice - 2003 Conference Video, 4 (Box 10)
- Local 82 -- Luchando para El Sueno Americano, 5 (Box 10)
- America Needs Human Rights, 6 (Box 10)
- Voice@Work Flash Animation -- September 2003, 7 (Box 10)
- 2000 Annual Meeting, 8 (Box 10)
- From the Mountains to the Maquiladoras -- a TIRN Educational Video, 9 (Box 10)
- International Machinists Union -- News Highlights Jobs with Justice - June 6, 1991 (Dub), 10 (Box 10)
- Client C.W.A. -- Program Justicia, 11 (Box 10)
- JwJ News Highlights -- June-December 1987, 12 (Box 10)
- Kentucky - Sonora Worker Exchange -- Southern Arizona Alliance for Economic Justice, 13 (Box 10)
- JwJ News Highlights -- June-December 1987, 14 (Box 10)
- Community Action for Workers' Rights, 15 (Box 10)
- Community Action for Workers' Rights, 16 (Box 10)
- Community Action for Workers' Rights, 17 (Box 10)
- Danger Ahead! -- Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 18 (Box 10)
- Jobs with Justice -- Tape #1, 19 (Box 10)
- Jobs with Justice -- Tape #2, 20 (Box 10)
- JwJ - WRB -- March 2004, 21 (Box 10)
- Biotech Rally Bottom -- March 2000; Spontaneous Celebrations, 22 (Box 10)
- Jobs with Justice: Community Action for Workers' Rights, 23 (Box 10)
- Another World is Possible: North American Voices at the World Social Forum, 1 (Box 11)
- Unemployment Benefits Rally and Picket, Dept. of Labor (tape 3 of 3), 2 (Box 11)
- Communication Workers of America, Jobs with Justice Narration - Channel 1 Narration, Channel 2 Slate -- 4/28/2003, 3 (Box 11)
- Jobs with Justice - Bellefontaine Park Rally - 9/23/2005, 4 (Box 11)
  roll 3
- Jobs with Justice - Belle fontaine Park Rally - 9/23/2005, 5 (Box 11)
  roll 2
- Jobs with Justice - Belle fontaine Park Rally -- 9/23/2005, 6 (Box 11)
  roll 1
- Jobs with Justice - Workers rights in the Global Economy - Annual Meeting 2005, 7 (Box 11)
  tape 4 of 6
- Jobs with Justice - Workers rights in the Global Economy - Annual Meeting 2005, 8 (Box 11)
  tape 5 of 6
- Jobs with Justice - Workers rights in the Global Economy - Annual meeting 2005, 9 (Box 11)
  tape 6 of 6
- Another World is Possible: North American Voices at the World Social Forum, 10 (Box 11)
- Unemployment Benefits Rally and Picket, Department of Labor, Washington, DC, 11 (Box 11)
  Tape 2 of 3
- Kentucky - Sonora Worker Exchange -- Southern Arizona Alliance for Economic Justice, 12 (Box 11)
- Jobs with Justice - 2001 Conference Video, 13 (Box 11)
- Unemployment Benefits Rally and Picket, Department of Labor, Washington, DC, 14 (Box 11)
  tape 1 of 3
- September 2001 recordings [no other specific information on tapes] -- tape 1-8, 15 (Box 11)
- JWJ051207B1 [ no other information on tape], 16 (Box 11)
- PARE ALCA - 11/2003, 17 (Box 11)
- Unlabeled, 18 (Box 11)
- DC WRB Hearing 3/31/2004, 19 (Box 11)
- A Day's Work, A Day's Pay -- 11/24/1997, 20 (Box 11)
- New York Market (#1) -- 1/30/2002, 21 (Box 11)
- Cabin Creek Center - Emergency Drive -- 10/8/1991, 22 (Box 11)
- Frank Ianna - Workplace of the future --- 3/5/1999, 23 (Box 11)
- The Hearings on the Work Experience Program - Nov. 20, 1996, 24 (Box 11)
- Unlabeled, 25 (Box 11)
- National Worker's Rights Board Hearing on Social Security No-Match Letters, 1 (Box 12)
- National Workers' Rights Board Hearing on Social Security No-Match Letters, 1 (Box 13)
- ACUFF, 1 (Box 14)
- National Workers' Rights Board - Hearing on Wal-Mart: Jobs with Justice Highlights-- September 24, 2005, St. Louis, MO, 1 (Box 15)
- National Workers' Rights Board - Hearing on Wal-Mart: Jobs with Justice Highlights -- September 24, 2005, St. Louis, MO, 1 (Box 16)
- Jobs with Justice Highlights - National Workers' Rights Board: Hearing on Wal-Mart, 1 (Box 17)
- Jobs with Justice Highlights - National Workers' Rights Board: Hearing on Wal-Mart, 1 (Box 18)
- Stewart Acuff, Organizing Director, AFL-CIO - Jobs with Justice, National Annual Meeting - September 24, 2005, 1 (Box 19)
- Stewart Acuff, Organizing Director, AFL-CIO - Jobs with Justice, National Annual Meeting - September 24, 2005, 1 (Box 20)
- Beehive Collective: Graphics for the Commons, 1 (Box 21)
- Nan O'Malley: Travelin' Light, 1 (Box 22)
- Young and Younger - George Mann, Julius Margolin, 1 (Box 23)
- The Bones of Contention: Power, 1 (Box 24)
- Melinda E. Pittman in Paradise Flossed, 1 (Box 25)
- We Ain't Gonna Give it Back, 1 (Box 26)
- This is What Democracy Looks Like: Wisconsin's Worker Uprising, 1 (Box 27)
- Raise Hope for Congo, 1 (Box 28)
- Mini-disk of NWRB - Hearing on WalMart, 1 (Box 29)
  Mini Disc
- Inside Out / Charlie King, 1 (Box 30)
- Don't Be Related to Walmart: Flash Mob at Time Warner Center - 4/8/2011, 1 (Box 31)
- MO JWJ, 1 (Box 32)
- Kazpona Akter Testimonial: Worker Truth Tour, NYC Stop - 3/31/2011, 1 (Box 33)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 34)
- Mystery of the Missing Jobs Plan, Albany, NY - 6/14/2011, 1 (Box 35)
- May 12: March on Wall St., 1 (Box 36)
- Trade Deals & Construction Workers - Summer 2002, 1 (Box 37)
- CWA Teleconference on New US-India Report on Call Center Outsourcing: Candice Johnson - 10/17/2006, 1 (Box 38)
- Trade Deals & Construction Workers - Summer 2002, 1 (Box 39)
- Celebrating 15 Years: New York Jobs with Justice, 1 (Box 40)
- Hasta la Victorial: The Occupation at Republic Windows & Doors, 1 (Box 41)
- S26 - A Global Day of Action - 9/26/2000, 1 (Box 42)
- S26 - A Global Day of Action - 9/26/2000, 1 (Box 43)
- S26 - A Global Day of Action - 9/26/2000, 1 (Box 44)
- Jobs With Justice - 5/2/2008, 1 (Box 45)
- Jobs With Justice - 5/2/2008, 1 (Box 46)
- Labor Forum on Immigration - Portland JWJ - June 2006, 1 (Box 47)
- Labor Bring on Immigration - 2006 // Portland JWJ - June 2006, 1 (Box 48)
- Walk for Justice - Southbend - 5/5/2005, 1 (Box 49)
- Wal-Mart Segment on Today Show - 11/01/2005, 1 (Box 50)
- Angels in the Dust Movie, 1 (Box 51)
- JWJ Worker Rights Board - April 2005 -- The Right to Organize, 1 (Box 52)
- AFSCME Goshen, Highway Worker Rally - 6/25/2005, 1 (Box 53)
- Affordable Health Care for All: Moving Beyond Political Deadlock, 1 (Box 54)
- IWFR/ #1, 1 (Box 55)
- IWFR/ #2, 1 (Box 56)
- Jobs With Justice - Wal-Mart Banking, 1 (Box 57)
- East New Yorkers Against Walmart - 7/11/2011, 1 (Box 58)
- Hope Will Win Over Fear: The World Social Forums, 1 (Box 59)
- Worker's Testimonials - Ginny, 1 (Box 61)
- Radio Free Nashville - Roundtable with Jack Irby, Katharine Dunn, Host, 1 (Box 62)
- Start of meeting - - 10/25/1997, 1 (Box 63)
- Last 45 min. (no other information), 1 (Box 64)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 65)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 66)
- KY-Mex Worker Exchange -- 6/7/2002, 1 (Box 67)
- from 'Leaves me blind', 1 (Box 68)
- JWJ - UCAW and CAU -- 4/18/1971, 1 (Box 69)
- Communication Workers of America 5/1/1991, 1 (Box 70)
- Jobs with Justice - Workers Rights Board -- 10/24/1997 [side 1 & 2], 1 (Box 71)
- "Hogs At The Trough": Campaign for an America that works, 1 (Box 72)
- Ride the Rockies, Denver Post Boycott, 1 (Box 73)
- Songs For the Labor Movement, 1 (Box 74)
- Angels: The Next Generation, 1 (Box 75)
- Workers Rights Board -- 10/24/1997 [side 3 & 4], 1 (Box 76)
- Supredrive! -- The Superfund Singers, 1 (Box 77)
- Jobs with Justice - Workers Rights Board -- 10/24/1997 [side 1 & 2], 1 (Box 78)
- Si Kahn: I'll Be There, 1 (Box 79)
- Jobs With Justice, 1 (Box 80)
- Jobs With Justice: Radio Spots Nashville, TN - 1987, 1 (Box 81)
- AFSCME, ANR, April 2002, 1 (Box 82)
- AFSCME, ANR, April 2002, 1 (Box 82)
- Day 7 Strike -- tape 6, 1 (Box 83)
- Healy CW Riot -- tape 8, 2 (Box 83)
- LW meets BOD -- tape 7, 3 (Box 83)
- JWJ250308A1 -- SSA Shots, 4 (Box 83)
- Unlabeled, 5 (Box 83)
- Unlabeled -- tape is in bad shape, 6 (Box 83)
- Hunger Strike - day 4-6 -- Tape 3, 7 (Box 83)
- Pegioias -- tape 5, 8 (Box 83)
- Dragged out & baby we won! -- tape 12, 9 (Box 83)
- Jobs with Justice - Community Action for Workers' Rights Final, 10 (Box 83)
- Day 4 - Strike - Spiros - Tape 10, 11 (Box 83)
- Living Wage Rally - 1/29/2005 -- tape 9, 12 (Box 83)
- JWJ WRB Video, 13 (Box 83)
- Elmwood - May '04, 2004; 14 (Box 83)
- SOA 2003, 15 (Box 83)
- SOA, 16 (Box 83)
- LW Joe --, 17 (Box 83)
- Portland, 18 (Box 83)
- Health Care Justice #1 / 6/21/2003 - Opening Invocation, 19 (Box 83)
- Columbia - 2/9/2003 #2, 20 (Box 83)
- SFL JWJ WRB -- 10/15/2004, 21 (Box 83)
- DC JWJ - D Cohn -- Event @Sister Space, 22 (Box 83)
- JWJ Grinch Award - 2000, 23 (Box 83)
- Living Wage - End - 5/30/2001, 24 (Box 83)
- Living Wage - 5/2/2001, 25 (Box 83)
- Prov. Collage - 4/4/2002, 26 (Box 83)
- Living Wage - 3/5/2002, 27 (Box 83)